freundcontainer.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Freund Container, a Division of Berlin Packaging

**What information do we collect?**

We collect personal information about you, such as your name, credit card information, postal address, telephone, and email address when you voluntarily provide such information to us. We may collect personal information from you when you contact us using our online contact form or if you send us an email. We may also collect personal information from you if you choose to fill out one of our surveys or if you choose to register on one of our Websites. We may also collect non-personal information from you when you visit or interact with our Websites, such as Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, data and time of visit, referral page, the pages you visit, and other information. 

**What do we use your information for?**

We use the personal information we collect about you to respond to your questions or to provide you with the products, services, or information that you request. We may also use your personal information to keep you informed about our new products and services offerings or to tell you about upcoming events. If you wish you opt-out of receiving promotional or marketing materials from us, please see the “Your Choices” section below. We may use non-personal information to ensure the technical performance and functioning of the Websites and to personalize your experience on our Websites by delivering you more relevant content. 

To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used for marketing purposes. We may combine your email address with other information (such as demographic or lifestyle information) from our files and other sources. However, we allow only your email address or other information that it has been combined with to be used by us and others for marketing purposes. Marketing purposes include, but are not limited to:
> 
>   * Sending you relevant email or direct marketing messages and offers from companies with whom you have a prior business relationship 
>   * Conducting surveys and other marketing research studies 
>   * Modeling and analysis 
> 

**Your Choices**

If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional or marketing materials from us, update or change your information, or delete personal information you provided to us, please let us know by either calling our toll free number 1.800.363.9822, sending us an email at [customerservice@freundcontainer.com](mailto:customerservice@freundcontainer.com), or by writing to us at the mailing address at the bottom of this policy. Please provide us with your full name and address (or other applicable contact information) when contacting us. Please note that it may take several days to process your opt-out request and that you may continue to receive promotional or marketing materials during this time. Also, please note that opting-out of receiving will not preclude us from sending you other types of non-promotional messages, such as emails about your registered account. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies or other Web Technologies?**

Our Website uses cookies and other web technologies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer or device by a website’s server. When you visit or interact with our Websites, we may use cookies to improve your experience on our Website. For example, cookies help us understand whether or not you are already logged in as you click throughout our Website. We do not use cookies to collect and/or store your personal information. Most browsers have options that allow you to choose what cookies can be placed on your computer and to delete or disable cookies, but setting a browser to reject cookies may affect and limit your experience on our Websites. 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

We use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Site visitors may opt out of the cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page. Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions. We do not require that you accept cookies and/or you may withdraw your consent to our use of cookies at any time by adjusting your browser's privacy settings, however, some functionality on our Website (e.g. “functionality cookies”), our check-out process, and products and services may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies ( e.g. “necessary cookies”). You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third Party Websites and Social Networks**

Our Websites may link to websites that are not under our control, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any linked site not controlled by us. For example, we provide a number of links to associations and institutes that are part of the packaging industry, as well as other industries. We also provide links to social networks, such as Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. We are not responsible for the privacy practices at these external websites or their use of your information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies for these websites. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.freundcontainer.com](http://www.freundcontainer.com/)

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may update our privacy policy at any time by posting updated text on this webpage. We display an Effective Date at the top of this policy so that it will be easier for you to know when there has been a change. Accordingly, we recommend that you check this privacy policy from time to time so that you are aware of our most current privacy practices. Each time you access, use, or browse one of our Websites, you signify your acceptance of the then-current version of this privacy policy. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Freund Container & Supply  
4200 Commerce Court, Suite 206  
Lisle, IL 60532  
United States  
customerservice@freundcontainer.com  
800-363-9822
